villagehatshop.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy & Security - Village Hat Shop

At Village Hat Shop, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, which is why we do not sell, rent, or loan any personal identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party.

### 100% Secure Checkout

At Village Hat Shop, you have the choice to use our 100% Secure Checkout or PayPal. We accept all major credit cards Visa, Master Card, American Express and Discover card.

### What Information We Collect

In order to process your order efficiently, we collect the following information: name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number ("Personal Information") when you place an order with us. This information is used solely by Village Hat Shop and is stored in a secure environment. Under certain circumstances we do also collect the user's IP address, but only when we suspect that credit card fraud may have occurred. We also periodically conduct surveys of visitors to our website. This helps us better understand what our customers would like to see from us. We use this information for internal marketing research purposes. We may contact a visitor who responded to a survey for more information, but only if that visitor has told us that they don't mind being contacted.

### Use of Information that You Provide

At Village Hat Shop, we collect Personal Information only for the purposes of fulfilling orders, providing a high level of customer service, gaining knowledge internally regarding what our customers want and mailing circulars and special offers from Village Hat Shop. We do not give or sell Personal Information to any other party. If at any time you do not want to receive offers and/or circulars from us, you can always remove yourself from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to VillageHatShop.com

### Opt-out Email policy

We ask that you tell us when you do not wish to receive periodic emails from us. We will only send email for customer service purposes and to those visitors who have indicated that they wish to receive other types of email from us. If at any time you wish to stop receiving email from us at any time, you can always remove your name from our mailing list by sending us an email requesting that you wish to unsubscribe.

### Security of the Information You Provide

Among our top priorities is keeping your Personal Information secure. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which provides the highest level of security currently available for secure transactions, to encrypt all of your Personal Information before it is transmitted to us. Encrypted information cannot be read or recorded as it travels over the Internet. You can tell you are sending information securely by the unbroken key icon or closed lock icon that should appear at the bottom of your internet browser's window (depending on what browser you use). These icons will appear when you are placing an order on our website. In addition, you will see our site address change slightly, from http: to https: indicating a secure server connection is being used.

Additionally, access to your Personal Information is provided only to our employees and agents who have a need to know such information for the purpose of fulfilling your order and offering our high level of customer service. The computers that store your Personal Information are located in a separate facility which employs the latest in firewall and security technology.

### Use of Cookies

Our website uses "cookie" and "web beacon" technology. We use cookies and web beacons to identify your device, provide website user authentication, conduct fraud prevention and management services, distinguish you from other visitors, record your IP address and understand your use of our site, and identify the name of the Web site from which you linked to Village Hat Shop. This information is used for fulfilling contracts with our business partners, and to help us serve you better by improving our website design, as well as our products, services, and promotions. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available. A web beacon is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image and is used in conjunction with a cookie. 

When you visit our website, we may use both a session and a persistent cookie. This Village Hat Shop-placed cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track your usage of our website and in some cases, your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is only saved in this Village Hat Shop-placed cookie if you register with us. A web beacon allows us to capture certain additional types of information about a visitor's actions on a web site, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time, date, duration and number of page views, a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed, and details about any items that were purchased. 

If you register with us, this Village Hat Shop-placed cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our website and provides you with access to your account information. If you save your information with or order from us, we may also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. If you have not saved your information with or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. You can disable cookies at any time by using your browser options; however, if you turn off cookies, we will not be able to track your order or enable you to make a purchase from our website. In addition, we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user to allow you access to your account information. 

We may use Flash Cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) or other similar technologies. A Flash cookie is a small data file placed on a computer using Adobe Flash technology that may be built into your computer or downloaded by you to your computer. We use these technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience, facilitate processes, personalize and store your settings. Flash cookies may help our website visitors to, for example, set volume preference associated with a video experience, play games and perform surveys. They help us improve our sites by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to customers. We do not use Flash cookies for marketing or behavioral targeting purposes. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies and the cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. [Learn how](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html) to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies or other similar technologies, please be aware that you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under 13 years old please do not provide your information on our website.

If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to Village Hat Shop for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files. 

### Your Acceptance of these Terms

By using our website, you consent to Village Hat Shop's privacy policy. If you do not consent to the Privacy Policy, please do not use our website.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on our website. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on **09-10-2013**

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [contact us](https://www.villagehatshop.com/content/8/contact-us.html).
